<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<preferences>
  <panel name="General">
	  <preference>
		<name>Dialogue System</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Use Dialogue System</editor_label>
		<description>Selecting this item will enable communication with a Natural Language system. The system may not be available at all times or with all tutors.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Invoke Browser on External URL</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Invoke Browser on External URL</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is selected, then whenever a student action traverses a specially-marked link in the Behavior Graph, the system will try to invoke the machine's default web browser. The URL for the browser is formed from the External URL for Link Traversal (below) and link-specific data.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>External URL for Edge Traversal</name>
		<class>java.lang.String</class>
		<value></value>
		<editor_label>External URL for Link Traversal</editor_label>
		<description>This item gives the system-wide fixed portion of the URL for the Invoke Browser on External URL preference (above).</description>
	  </preference>
      <preference>
		<name>Login Window</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<!--DEPLOY_TUTOR Use Login Window--><value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Use Login Window</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is set, then the login window will be used to ask the student to enter a login name for the purpose of logging. Otherwise, the system user name will be used. This option applies only when the user interface is built from CTAT Java components.</description>
	  </preference>
      <preference>
		<name>Student Confirm Quit Question</name>
		<class>java.lang.String</class>
		<value>Do you want to save your work and log out?</value>
		<editor_label>Student Confirm Quit Question</editor_label>
		<description>This is the text displayed on a confirmation dialogue when the student tries to quit a Java tutor. If empty, then no confirmation dialogue is shown.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
	    <name>Show Tutor Type Save Popup</name>
	    <class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Show Tutor Type Save Dialog</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is selected, then attempting to save a graph (brd file) with a new Tutor Type will prompt the display of a confirmation dialog.</description>
	  </preference>
      <preference>
		<name>Projects Directory</name>
		<class>edu.cmu.pact.Preferences.FileBrowser</class>
		<value></value>
		<editor_label>Default Projects Folder</editor_label>
		<description>This folder, together with the folders within it, is the default top-level location for files created while authoring. If the value is a relative pathname, it is relative to the folder from which the current student interface was loaded ${studentInterface.url}. If the value is empty or no interface is loaded, the location is relative to the current working directory ${user.dir}.</description>
	  </preference>
      <preference>
		<name>Problem Directory</name>
		<class>edu.cmu.pact.Preferences.FileBrowser</class>
		<value></value>
		<editor_label>Cognitive Model Folder</editor_label>
		<description>This folder is the location for files to be read while executing. Unless explicitly set, it is the folder from which the current Java-language student interface was loaded ${studentInterface.url} or the location of the last behavior graph loaded.</description>
	  </preference>
  </panel>
  <panel name="Logging">
	  <preference>
		<name>EnableLogService</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Enable Logging Service (Flash tutors)</editor_label>
		<description>If set, then log messages received by the Tutoring Service from a Flash tutor will be saved in the Disk Logging Directory specified below.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>EnableLogForwarding</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
 		<value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Forward Logging Service Data (Flash tutors)</editor_label>
		<description>If the Logging Service is enabled, then enabling this preference will cause the Tutoring Service to also forward log messages to the Logging Server URL specified below.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Use OLI Logging</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<!--DEPLOY_TUTOR Log to Remote Server--><value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Log to Remote Server (Java or Flash tutors)</editor_label>
		<description>If set, then logging messages will be generated by the Java server and sent to the log server whose address is in the Logging Server URL specified below. Note: For Flash tutors this is an alternative to forwarding via the Logging Service (above), but the log entries will lack client-side time and hint information.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Use Disk Logging</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<!--DEPLOY_TUTOR Log to Disk--><value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Log to Disk (Java or Flash tutors)</editor_label>
		<description>If set, then logging messages will be generated by the Java server and recorded in disk files in the Disk Logging Directory specified below. Note: For Flash tutors this is an alternative to logging via the Logging Service (above), but the log entries will lack client-side time and hint information.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>enableAuthorLogging</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Enable Author Logging (Java or Flash)</editor_label>
		<description>If set, then author actions will be logged when logging is turned on.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>OLI Logging URL</name>
		<class>java.lang.String</class>
		<!--DEPLOY_TUTOR Logging Server URL--><value>http://learnlab.web.cmu.edu/log/server</value>
		<editor_label>Logging Server URL</editor_label>
		<description>The network address of the logging server.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Disk Logging Directory</name>
		<class>edu.cmu.pact.Preferences.FileBrowser</class>
		<!--DEPLOY_TUTOR Disk Logging Directory--><value>.</value>
		<editor_label>Disk Logging Directory</editor_label>
		<description>The path name for the directory in which disk logging files will be stored. If the value is a relative pathname, it is relative to the current directory where the authoring tools (or Tutoring Service) was started.  The value "." (dot, by itself) indicates this directory.  The current directory is ${user.dir}.</description>
	  </preference>
  </panel>
  <panel name="Behavior Graph">
	  <preference>
		<name>Case Sensitive</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Case Sensitive Exact Matching</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is set, then the student's input must match the case of the demonstrated input when using the Exact Matcher. Otherwise, the input case is ignored.  Matchers other than Exact Matcher are not affected.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>suppressStudentFeedback</name>
		<class>edu.cmu.pact.BehaviorRecorder.ProblemModel.FeedbackEnum</class>
		<value>Show All Feedback</value>
		<editor_label>Suppress Student Feedback</editor_label>
		<description>This item determines if and when tutor feedback (hints and correct/incorrect indications) is displayed to the student.  With the default setting, &lt;b&gt;Show All Feedback&lt;/b&gt;, the tutor displays feedback immediately as the student works each step. With &lt;b&gt;Hide All Feedback&lt;/b&gt;, the tutor never displays feedback; this can be useful, for instance, in quizzes.  With &lt;b&gt;Delay Feedback&lt;/b&gt;, the tutor will display feedback only when the student presses the Done button, and then only if the problem is incomplete because some steps are incorrect or left undone.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Commutativity</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Unordered Mode</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is set, the student can perform the actions in the behavior graph in any order.  Otherwise, the actions must be performed in the order shown in the graph.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>hintPolicy</name>
		<class>edu.cmu.pact.BehaviorRecorder.ProblemModel.HintPolicyEnum</class>
		<value>Use Both Kinds of Bias</value>
		<editor_label>Hint Policy</editor_label>
		<description>This item determines how hints are chosen in example-tracing tutors.  With the default setting, &lt;b&gt;Use Both Kinds of Bias&lt;/b&gt;, the tutor will first try to choose a hint that addresses a student's immediately-preceding error, then try for a hint on the user interface component presently selected, and finally default to show the hint on the best next step in the behavior graph. With the settings &lt;b&gt;Bias Hints by Prior Error Only&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;Bias Hints by Current Selection Only&lt;/b&gt;, the tutor's first choice for a hint (before the default choice) will depend only on the student's prior error or present selection, respectively.  With &lt;b&gt;Always Follow Best Path&lt;/b&gt;, the tutor's choice for a hint will depend only on the behavior graph and ignore any prior error or current selection.</description>
	  </preference>
	  	  <preference>
		<name>Lock Widgets</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Lock Widgets on Correct Action</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is set, the widgets will not allow new input after the student has performed a correct action. Otherwise, a student may change a value after a correct answer.</description>
	  </preference>
      <preference>
		<name>Highlight Right Widget</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Highlight Right Selection</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is set, then in ordered Example-Tracing tutors, a warning will be sent to the Student Interface if the student works on the wrong selection. The right selection will be highlighted.</description>
	  </preference>
    </panel>
  <panel name="Behavior Recorder">
	  <preference>
		<name>Group Dragging</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Use Group Dragging</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is set, dragging one node in the graph will drag all child nodes as well.  Otherwise, dragging one node will cause only that node to move.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Set Preferred Path</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Allow Changing Preferred Path</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is set, then the author can designate links in the graph as the preferred path. Otherwise, the author cannot change this designation.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Enable Edge Traversal Counts</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Enable Link Traversal Counts</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is set, then the Behavior Recorder will count link traversals in Demonstrate mode.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Always Link States</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>false</value>
		<editor_label>Always Link Similar States</editor_label>
		<description>If this item is set, then in Demonstrate mode, the Behavior Recorder will never prompt the author about whether to link states when it detects that the current state of the student interface matches an existing state; instead, the Behavior Recorder will always link the matched states.  If this item is unset, then the Behavior Recorder will prompt the author to ask whether to link to a matched state or to create a new state.</description>
	  </preference>
          
<!-- Added by EJ Ryu on 05/02/06  -->
<!-- won't be used yet
	<preference>
		<name>Maximum Number of Student Actors</name>
		<class>java.lang.Integer</class>
		<value>1</value>
		<editor_label>Maximum Number of Student Actors</editor_label>
		<description>Sets the maxmum number of students to collarborate on this problem.</description>
	  </preference>
-->
<!--
	  <preference>
		<name>Force Scaffolding</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Force Scaffolding</editor_label>
		<description>If force scaffolding is set, then the original question will be disabled and the student will be forced to finish the scaffolding questions. If force scaffolding is unset, then the original question is not disabled and the student can go back and answer the original question without completing the scaffolding.</description>
	  </preference>
-->
    </panel>
  <panel name="Jess Console">
	  <preference>
		<name>Chain</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Chain</editor_label>
		<description>Turns on Chaining in the Jess Console.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Firable</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Firable</editor_label>
		<description>Turns on Firable option in the Jess Console.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Break on Exceptions</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Break on Exceptions</editor_label>
		<description>Break when an exception occurs in the Jess Console.</description>
	  </preference>
  </panel>
  <panel name="Conflict Tree">
	  <preference>
		<name>Tree Depth</name>
		<class>java.lang.Integer</class>
		<value>5</value>
		<editor_label>Maximum Depth of Tree</editor_label>
		<description>This item limits the number of times a rule can be chained in the Conflict Tree.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Max Buggy Rules</name>
		<class>java.lang.Integer</class>
		<value>4</value>
		<editor_label>Maximum Number of Bug Rules</editor_label>
		<description>This item limits the number of bug rules displayed in the Conflict Tree.</description>
	  </preference>
	  <preference>
		<name>Use Salience</name>
		<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
		<value>true</value>
		<editor_label>Use Salience</editor_label>
		<description>This item instructs the production system to use salience.</description>
	  </preference>	  
  </panel>
  <preference>
	<name>Match Parentheses</name>
	<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
	<value>false</value>
	<editor_label>Match Parentheses</editor_label>
	<description>If this item is selected the built-in Production Rule Editor will highlight matching parentheses. Use of this option may slow response time with medium-to-large rule files.</description>
  </preference>
  <preference>
	<name>Highlight Comments</name>
	<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
	<value>false</value>
	<editor_label>Highlight Comments</editor_label>
	<description>If this item is selected the Production Rule Editor will highlight comments in your code. Use of this option may slow response time with medium-to-large rule files.</description>
  </preference>
  <preference>
	<name>Highlight Keywords</name>
	<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
	<value>false</value>
	<editor_label>Highlight Keywords</editor_label>
	<description>If this item is selected the Production Rule Editor will highlight keywords in your code. Use of this option may slow response time with medium-to-large rule files.</description>
  </preference>
  <preference>
	<name>Confirm Pre-commands</name>
	<class>java.lang.Boolean</class>
	<value>true</value>
	<editor_label>Confirm Pre-commands</editor_label>
	<description>Prompt the user before executing a pre-command.</description>
  </preference>
</preferences>
